oh fu you have a zodiac according to the drawn not
ой фу у тебя зодиака по нарисованным не
nicotine a rag of the rear
никотина тряпка задней
axle I put on I am from Rostov and where
оси я поставил по я из ростова и откуда
we and Russia are from Rostov and you are
мы и россии я уже из ростова а вы
generally
вообще
bryanka
брянке
I now want Saratov as a
я сейчас саратове желая как беженец
refugee when there are a lot of refugees but for about
когда много беженец но примерно уже
three or four months and why are you  a refugee
три-четыре месяца а почему ты беженец
because there is a war there, it turns out
потому что там идет война из получается
russia had a war and
россии пришлось войну и
no how not but
нет как нет а
how look ukraine 8 years trying to
как смотри украина 8 лет пытался
destroy the donbass donbass this is ukraine
уничтожить донбасс донбасс это украина
donbass shoes to
донбасса туфли на
eat ukraine is divided into two parts
съесть украина разделена на две части
donbass and russia and ukraine how
донбасс и россии и украины тебе сколько
old are you not 13 years old i lived before  tests was born in
лет не 13 лет я жил до тесты родился в
ukraine yes yes but how did you turn out then you
украине да да а как ты получился тогда
don’t live in ukraine and now i live in ukraine
не в украине живешь вот и живу в украине
it was ukraine i didn’t recognize i don’t
это было украина я не признавал я не
admit that i was born in ukraine i don’t lose all the documents i do
признаю что я родился в украине мне все
n’t have ukrainian documents
документы нет украинских документов не
and look who changed your
опадать и смотри кто тебе поменял
documents i’m on  Russian documents
документы я на российских документах
I find this is Russia where
нахожу этот это россии откуда там
did Russia come from because we have made
взялась россия потому что у нас сделали
Russian passports peanuts tekke
российские паспорта арахис текке
certificate will be sent to where did you get it in
свидетельство отправят к откуда у вас в
ukraine
украине взялись российские паспорта и
I didn’t live in Ukraine I lived in the
лесистых виде я не в украине жил я жил в
LPR consider you didn’t live in Ukraine for
лнр рассмотри не ты жил в украине на
giving birth to this one in Ukraine, it’s true, but
родив этой в украине правда но
Russian passports have appeared since 2014
российские паспорта для появились с 2014
, but how did you get Easter
года а как как у тебя появился пасху
where did the Russian passport appear in the
откуда российский паспорт появился в
fourteenth year there  in ukraine if you
четырнадцатом году там в украине если ты
would have lived there, but what
жил бы родился там а то что я как
happened to me, you lived in ukraine and
получилось вот ты жил в украине так и у
you have a ukrainian ambassador a russian passport
тебя украинский посол российский паспорт
will appear in a loop i have not 5 years old my
появится в петле у меня не 5 лет у моей
mother has a Russian regiment your mother
мамы есть российский полку твоей мамы
has information there.
у тебя там сведение .
how the signboard
как вот вывеску
came russia with the war began to start
пришла россия с войной начала начать
expanding the war it’s not russia’s fault for everything
расширять войну не виноваты во всем
but what if we lived in the
россия ну а как если мы 8 лет жили в
basement for 8 years tracy brian and why
подвале трейси брайан а почему началась
did this start and when did you live in the basement
вот этого и на когда вы жили в подвале
because we but because we lived
потому что мы а потому что мы жили себе
peacefully  ukraine started shooting like in
мирно украина начал стрелять как в
russia how would you like for which russia
россии как вы бы по какой россии
well okay power-up socket where
ну ладно power-up розетка откуда
did it come from she was also the luhansk
появилось это она тоже была луганская
region of ukraine
область украины
what moment did she suddenly become lnr about what
какой момент она вдруг стала лнр о каком
moment she did not become aqua in which she became
моменте она не стала aqua в каком стала
well because she sat down and from  ukraine
ну потому что она садилась а от украине
didn’t want to live ukraine in april it started
хотела не жить украина апреле это начала
shelling like look i remember i remember
обстрел как смотри я помню я помню 2014
2014 so militants came from russia so they
год так пришли боевики из россии так
started there no yes i yes absolutely yes
начали там нет да я да абсолютно да вот
look how the war in donbass started
смотри с чего началась война на донбассе
seized the
боевик стрелков так зашел и захватил
city of slavyansk
город славянск
no and from what it was given that's what date
нет а с чего это далось вот какой даты
why russia is to blame why because
почему виновата россия почему потому что
russia will do you well
россия сделает вы ну
well russia don't even if she did
ну россия не делают даже если она делала
she broadcasts what sv  oh territory like
она вещает чего свою территорию как как
its own territory LPR once again
свою территорию лнр еще раз с какой из
since when did it become the territory of russia well
каких пор это стало территории россии ну
okay i don’t deny alanare it’s not
ладно я не отрицаю аланаре это не
even ukraine to you but it’s russia it
украина тебе даже но это россия
turns out well i don’t know
получается ну я не знаю
you  there you can see the sensuality of the hand on the
да есть там видно чувственности руку на
Russian passport, so
российский паспорт так
even a good glow for Ted Russia has
даже хороший свечением для теда россия
nothing to do with turning it off and 2014 rock mom the
тут не причем выключаем и 2014 року мама
Russian passport of the act, then
российский паспорт акта то и
it happens to these children that
этим детям бывает в голову что там
Ukraine bombed them there and so on, so
украина их бомбила и так далее так что
you read them to tell the truth two
вы им почитаешь указывать правду два
transport  kids, here’s a bunch of jokes who
транспортных детки вот подколы куча кто
porsche and put on the donbass, this is
porsche и поставил на донбасс это
Ukraine, say a pier, and we’ll throw Ukraine, they
украина причала скажи и кидаем украина
started shelling them on whom, and
почала вас обстреливать их кого числа и
then
тогда
they, because what’s everything in the form of a start to the course, I’m
им ибо чем все в виде почала курсе я
Russian of the entire RES network, and then it
российские всей сети рэс ты и тогда то
was the fault below, and he’s the kid’s fault
внизу был вину а он это малышу вину
we hang rocky in tiksi and
висим рокки в тикси и
frames and all bloody Russian militants
кадры и весь кровью российские боевики
and other things inspire children with what wedge they were killed by
и тпр чем детям внушает чё клина их убил
his land
его земля
with a sword and watched to bathe her
мечом и следил купать ее
normally information poly  tika may
нормально информационная политика мае
buti natsik caviar territory dytyne
бути нацик территория икорницы дытыне
explain and tell allegedly as much as russia
пояснять и расскажет якобы мере россия
stole d test
крала д тесту
we wave and type of information don’t
мы моему да помахать и тип информации не
blame me for 1
вини за 1
more skin day but was angry at the word cry
еще кожен день но был зол от слова cry
like
пидпысуйтесь
this monterrey like
такой монтеррее ставьте лайк
and subscribe to dollars abs and 2 2
и подписывайтесь на долларов abs и 2 2